[

](https://seasonic.com/)

    [

    PRIME TX ATX 3.0
    
    1600 W1300 W](https://seasonic.com/atx3-prime-tx/)[

    PRIME PX ATX 3.0
    
    1600 W](https://seasonic.com/atx3-prime-px/)[

    PRIME FANLESS TX
    
    700 W600 W](https://seasonic.com/prime-fanless-tx/)[

    PRIME FANLESS PX
    
    500 W450 W](https://seasonic.com/prime-fanless-px/)[

    PRIME TX
    
    1600 W1300 W1000 W850 W750 W650 W](https://seasonic.com/prime-tx/)[

    PRIME PX
    
    1600 W1300 W1000 W850 W750 W650 W](https://seasonic.com/prime-px/)[

    PRIME GX
    
    1300 W1000 W850 W750 W650 W](https://seasonic.com/prime-gx/)

    [

    VERTEX PX
    
    1200 W1000 W850 W750 W](https://seasonic.com/vertex-px/)[

    VERTEX GX
    
    1200 W1000 W850 W750 W](https://seasonic.com/vertex-gx/)[

    VERTEX GX WHITE EDITION
    
    1200 W1000 W](https://seasonic.com/vertex-gx-white/)[

    VERTEX SAKURA
    
    1000 W](https://seasonic.com/vertex-sakura/)

    [

    FOCUS GX ATX 3.0
    
    1000 W850 W750 W](https://seasonic.com/atx3-focus-gx/)[

    FOCUS GX WHITE ATX 3.0
    
    1000 W850 W750 W](https://seasonic.com/atx3-focus-gx-white/)[

    FOCUS PX
    
    850 W750 W650 W550 W](https://seasonic.com/focus-px/)[

    FOCUS GX
    
    1000 W850 W750 W650 W550 W](https://seasonic.com/focus-gx/)[

    FOCUS GX WHITE EDITION
    
    1000 W850 W750 W](https://seasonic.com/focus-gx-white/)[

    FOCUS GM
    
    850 W750 W650 W550 W](https://seasonic.com/focus-gm/)[

    FOCUS SPX (2021)
    
    750 W650 W](https://seasonic.com/focus-spx-2021/)[

    FOCUS SGX (2021)
    
    750 W650 W550 W](https://seasonic.com/focus-sgx-2021/)

    [

    CORE GX
    
    650 W550 W500 W](https://seasonic.com/core-gx/)[

    CORE GM
    
    650 W550 W500 W](https://seasonic.com/core-gm/)[

    CORE GC
    
    650 W550 W500 W](https://seasonic.com/core-gc/)

    [

    G12 GM
    
    850 W750 W650 W550 W](https://seasonic.com/g12-gm/)[

    G12 GC
    
    850 W750 W650 W550 W](https://seasonic.com/g12-gc/)

    [

    B12 BM
    
    850 W750 W650 W550 W](https://seasonic.com/b12-bm/)[

    B12 BC
    
    850 W750 W650 W550 W](https://seasonic.com/b12-bc/)

    [

    CONNECT
    
    750 W](https://seasonic.com/connect/)[

    SYNCRO PSU
    
    850 W750 W650 W](https://seasonic.com/syncro-psu/)[

    A12
    
    700 W600 W500 W](https://seasonic.com/a12/)[

    ECO PLUS SERIES
    
    600 W500 W400 W](https://seasonic.com/eco-plus-series/)[

    S12II EVO
    
    450 W](https://seasonic.com/s12ii-evo/)[

    S12III
    
    650 W550 W500 W450 W](https://seasonic.com/s12iii/)

Search

 All Products News Other

Search

Privacy And Cookie Policy
=========================

This Privacy Policy describes how Sea Sonic Electronics, Ltd. (‘Sea Sonic’) collects, uses, stores, and shares personal data that you leave via your digital footprint or provide when you visit our website www.seasonic.com or use our other company related sites and services. We collect different types of information of the website’s visitors and our customers in order to communicate with them and to provide technical support. We use collected analytical data to improve our services, products and the website. Please read the following Privacy Policy and don’t hesitate to contact us if you have any questions.

### 1\. Collection of Personal Data

When you use the Seasonic website, you have the chance to register your Seasonic product by creating an account with us. We collect the following data about you:

* Your personal information
    * Name
    * Email
    * Country of residence
    * Username
    * Password
    * Possible consent to receiving our newsletter
* Information on your Seasonic product
    * Date of Purchase
    * Serial number
    * Proof of Purchase, if you choose to upload the document to our website

If you contact Seasonic Support, evoke your product warranty, participate in a promotional program or fill out one of our questionnaires, we may collect the following data to be able to answer a request from you or provide the necessary support:

* Your personal information
    * Name
    * Email
    * Shipping address
* Information on your Seasonic product
    * Date of Purchase
    * Serial number

If you provide personal information about persons other than yourself, you must ensure that you are given permission to provide us with the personal data of the relevant persons.

You can change or delete your Personal Data at any time by contacting the Sea Sonic Support Team at [\[email protected\]](https://seasonic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### 2\. Use of Personal Data

When you use our website and services, we collect personal data for the following purposes:

* Management of product registration and user accounts
* Warranty evocation and processing
* Customer support and communication
* Technical support and assistance
* Promotional marketing
* Statistical data and analysis to improve our products and services

The processing of personal data is often necessary to meet your requests or to perform our services. Sea Sonic will only use your personal data for marketing activities if you have given your explicit consent in advance.

### 3\. Storage

The information collected through Product Registration and Warranty Services is stored in the facilities of our service provider, InMotion Hosting. Sea Sonic will delete your personal data as soon as we no longer need these to achieve the above-mentioned purposes. We may, however, process your personal data anonymously for a longer period of time or if we are legally obliged or entitled to do so.

### 4\. Sharing of Personal Data

Sea Sonic will not sell, share, or otherwise distribute your Personal Data to third parties, except as provided in this Privacy Policy. All the data we collect is used for the purposes listed above. Personal Data may be transferred to third parties who act for or on our behalf, for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data were originally collected. These third parties have contracted with us to only use Personal Data for the agreed upon purpose, and not to sell or disclose your Personal Information to third parties, unless it may be required by law. On our website, we have implemented the products of different Data Processors, such as Cognito Forms and Zendesk, to assist in the communication with our customers and visitors to our website, as well as to improve our services.

### 5\. Permission

When you use our website, we may collect and process your personal data on the basis of your consent. You have the right to request changes or to entirely delete your personal data at any time. Please send an email to the Sea Sonic Support Team at [\[email protected\]](https://seasonic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) if you wish to do so. If you withdraw your consent, we will stop processing your personal data unless we have the right or the obligation to continue processing or storing your personal data on legal or regulatory basis. The withdrawal of your consent does not affect the legality of the processing prior to the withdrawal. If you withdraw your consent, you may not be able to make full use of the features offered on our website.

### 6\. Use of Cookies

We use cookies to gather statistical traffic information about the number and geographic location of visitors to our website, the most visited pages, and visitors’ browser types and operating systems. We collect such data to build a better user experience on our website and to improve our services. For example, by knowing the demographics of visitors from a certain country, we can localize the website for the specific audience.

We use Google Analytics and other similar technologies to generate anonymous statistical data of our website traffic. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics monitoring, please see more information here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

We have also implemented Facebook Pixel to generate targeted advertisements. For example, you may be shown an advertisement that may be relevant to you of a discount promotion of our products from an online store after you have visited our website. If you wish to opt-out of Facebook’s targeted ads on one or all websites, you can do so on Facebook’s [Ad Preferences page.](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen)

You can prevent cookie tracking on one or all websites by configuring your browser’s settings. Please consult your browser’s Help Page.

### 7\. Security

We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure an adequate level of security and collaborate with trusted third parties who properly handle your personal data. We make every effort to ensure the confidentiality and integrity of your personal data.

### 8\. Links to Other Websites

Our website pages may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content of other websites or for the procedures of third parties for the collection and processing of personal data. If you visit a third-party website, you must read the privacy policy and other relevant policies of the relevant website owner.

### 9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Sea Sonic reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy without prior notice based on substantial changes in legislation, new technical solutions, and to improve the functioning of the website. Such changes will be directly updated in this Privacy Policy.

### 10\. Contact

If you want us to update, correct or delete the personal data that we have registered about you or if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by sending an email to [\[email protected\]](https://seasonic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* Features
* Solutions

* Support
* About Seasonic

Sign up to our newsletter

Subscribe to our emails. No spam.

Subscribe

Follow us

© 2024 Sea Sonic. All rights reserved

Notice: JavaScript is required for this content.
